Guide to the Hasia Diner Papers, 1970-2012 MC.153
New York University Archives
Hasia Diner Papers
1960-2023
1970-1992
New York University Archives
Diner, Hasia R.
MC.153
52.94 Linear Feet in 34 record cartons, 38 manuscript boxes, and 2 half manuscript boxes
24 Gigabytes
Hasia R. Diner is a Professor of American Jewish History and the Director of the Goldstein-Goren Center for American Jewish History at NYU. Her research interests include American Jewish history, American immigration history, and women's history. The Hasia Diner Papers (1960-2023) includes Diner's research notes for her manuscripts.
Biographical Note
Hasia R. Diner is the Paul and Sylvia Steinberg Professor of American Jewish History at New York University, with a joint appointment in the departments of History and the Skirball Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies. She is also the Director of the Goldstein Goren Center for American Jewish History. Professor Diner received her Ph.D. in History from the University of Illinois-Chicago, her bachelor's degree in 1968 from the University of Wisconsin, and her master's degree from the University of Chicago in 1970.
Previously, Professor Diner was a professor in the Department of American Studies at the University of Maryland at College Park and between 1990-1991, she held a Fulbright Professorship at the University of Haifa in Israel. In 1998, Professor Diner won election to membership in the American Academy of Jewish Research and in 2004, she also became a member of the Society of American Historians. Professor Diner has been a Lilly Fellow at the Mary I. Bunting Institute at Radcliffe College and a fellow at the Shelby Cullom Davis Center for Historical Research at Princeton University.
Professor Diner has published many books and articles, including In the Almost Promised Land: American Jews and Blacks, 1915-1935 (1977, 1995), A Time For Gathering. 1820-1880: The Second Migration (1992), Erin's Daughters in America: Irish Immigrant Women in the Nineteenth Century (1984), The Lower Eastside Memories: A Jewish Place in America (2000), Hungering for America: Italian, Irish, and Jewish Foodways in the Age of Migration (2002), and We Remember with Reverance and Love: American Jews and the Myth of Silence after the Holocaust, 1945-1962 (2009).
Sources:
Hasia Diner, research notes.
Scope and Contents
The Hasia Diner Papers (1960-2023) includes research materials Professor Diner used when writing about American Jewish history, American immigration history, and American women's history. In addition to Professor Diner's handwritten notes, the collection contains photocopies of primary and secondary sources; and some monographs with Professor Diner's hand written notes. The collection also contains syllabi and lecture notes from courses Professor Diner has taught at NYU. Majority of the folder titles in the collection were transferred from Diner's original research folders.
Arrangement
This collection consists of one series and eight subseries, where each subseries represents on of Professor Diner's books. Folders contain notes and source material arranged by the author.
Series I: Research Notes
Subseries I.A: Erin's Daughters
Subseries I.B: In the Almost Promised Land
Subseries I.C: Jewish Self-Governance
Subseries I.D: A Time for Gathering
Subseries I.E: Hungering for America
Subseries I.F: Lower East Side Memories
Subseries I.G: We Remember with Reverance and Love
Subseries I.H: Roads Taken
Immediate Source of Acquisition
These records were transferred to the University Archives by Professor Hasia Diner in 1998, 2012, 2018, 2022, and 2024.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact New York University Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Appraisal
In June 2025,
Immigrants -- United States.; Sephardim -- United States -- History.; Jews -- United States -- History.; Research (document genres).; Judaism -- United States -- History.; United States -- Emigration and immigration.; Notes.; Reference sources.; Jews -- United States -- Social conditions.; United States -- Ethnic relations.; Irish American women -- History -- 19th century.; African Americans -- Relations with Jews; Jews -- United States -- History -- 19th century; Jews, German -- United States -- History -- 19th century.; Judaism -- United States -- History -- 19th century.; Books.; Diner, Hasia R.; New York University
- Series I: Research Notes
  - Subseries A: Erin's Daughter
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Education, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Famine, undated, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Ireland, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Labor, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Male-female relations, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Migration, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Women's Roles, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Employment, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Family in Ireland, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Ireland, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Irish women's support groups, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Trade unions, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Women and employment, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Chapter 6, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Chapter 6, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Family, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Services for Irish, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Services for women, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes: Women's social life, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Erin's Daughters research notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: In the Almost Promised Land
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Causes, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Chapter 2, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Chapter 3, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Final chapter, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research note, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Labor, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Music, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Sermons, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Chapter 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes: Chapter 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - In the Almost Promised Land research notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Jewish Self Governance
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Self Governance notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Notes on German Situation, 1960-1995 (Box 8)
    - Notes, 1960-1995 (Box 8)
    - Kaplan, 1960-1995 (Box 8)
    - Introduction and Chapter One, 1960-1995 (Box 8)
    - Footnotes, 1960-1995 (Box 8)
  - Subseries D: Time for Gathering
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Time For Gathering notes: photos, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Time For Gathering notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Hungering for America
    - Italians of San Francisco Photocopies, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Emergence of Italian American Photocopies, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Italians and Alcohol, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Italian Immigrant Foodways, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - An Italian Tragedy- notes and copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - The Heart is the Teacher- copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Pan-Italian Traditions- copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Notes on Italians, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Italian Opinion on America- copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Leone's Italian Cookbook-copies, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Notes on Italians and Food, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Olives on the Apple Tree- notes and copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The Grand Gennaro- notes and copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Italian Food Patterns- photocopies, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Italian American Communities- notes and copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Italian Immigrant- photocopies, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Notes on Italian Immigrants, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Copies of photographs and drawings, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Requests to order images, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Family Supper Painting, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Food Illustrations, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - The Jewish Ladies Home Journal, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Daniel Kotzin Dissertation Abstract, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - "An American Jewish Radical"- Dissertation by Daniel Kotzin, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Notes on Jewish Immigration, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Defense of Jewish Food, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - PreMARC Records on books, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Copyright information, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Photocopies of Jewish Food Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Notes on Jewish Food, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Jewish Holidays, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Notes and Articles on Jewish Culture, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Jewish Community life, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - NY Folklore Quarterly Articles, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Notes and articles on food, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - For Lena and Libe: Essay by Shelby Shapiro, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Shelby Shapiro's Thesis, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Food in American-Jewish Pop Culture, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - American Jewish Literature, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - American ideas about class- notes, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Notes on novelty, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Notes on Jewish Communities, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Notes and articles on Jewish Immigrants, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Food before Migration, undated (Box 14, File 3)
    - Jewish food notes and articles, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Society Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Roberta H. Schwartz, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Experiences, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Italian Bibliography Information, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Breckinridge Correspondence Material, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Jomarie Alano's research and paper, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Notes on Italian Society, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Excerpts from American Life Histories, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Book Reviews by Hasia Diner, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Pamphlets from Exhibits, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Index Cards (1 of 4), undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Index Cards (2 of 4), undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Index Cards (3 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Index Cards (4 of 4), undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Notes on Italian Food, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Notes on Italian Culture, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Notes on Italian Communities, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Italian Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - "Home Cooking" draft, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Roots of the Transplanted- photocopies, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Italian Photocopies (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Italian Ethics and Social Class, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Floppy Disk, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Italians from Connecticut Note Cards, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - List of Italian Food books from Boston, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Immigrants Speak- notes and copies, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Italian Immigrant Communities, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Newark's Little Italy- photocopies, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - NY Historical Society, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Italian Books, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - NYPL Resources, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Non Circulating Forms from Bobst, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Articles and Notes on Italian Immigrants, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Copies of Mount Allegro, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Articles from the Center of Immigration Studies, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - General Immigration Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Articles on Food Habits, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Home Economics Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Immigrant Health and Community Article, undayed (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Study of Americanization Forms, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Notes on Italian Social Life, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Notes on Italian Immigrant Life, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Italian American Immigrants Notes and Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Journal of Home Economics Articles, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Italian American Culture Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Italian Children and Women Notes and Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Research Items, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Dietary Studies in Chicago Report, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Notes on Gardens, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Sicilians in America, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Italian American Food Cultures Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Italian Family Life- Notes and Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Articles on Italian Diets, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Italian American Lifestyle- Articles and Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Jewish "Actual" Practices- Notes and articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Deja-Vu: Making Immigrants into Citizens Essay, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Criticisms on Jewish Cooking- Articles and Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Articles and Notes on Unions, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Unions- Tamiment Photocopies, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Jewishness Through Food- Articles and Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Lower East Side Oral Histories, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Jewish Food Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Jews and Food in the Eyes of Others (1 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Jews and Food in the Eyes of Others (2 of 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Food and Conflict Within Families, undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Health and Food Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Jewish Foodways, undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Jewish Food, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Women's Perspectives on Food, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Food Menus and Food Brands, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Subseries F: Lower East Side Memories
    - Princeton University Press Information, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Immigrants- Notes and Articles, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Eldridge Street (Lower East Side), undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Texts of Memory, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Early Version of Book for Talk, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Historic Lower East Side for History Chapter, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Historian Study the Lower East Side, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - References Not Used, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript Edits, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - The Time That Was Then- Notes and Copies, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Kosher Laws, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Presentation of Jewish Foodways, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Infrastructure and Novelty, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Oral Histories from Rochester, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Culture, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Rough Draft, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Notes, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Conclusion for Chapter 1, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - The American Hebrew- articles and notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - The American Hebrew- articles and notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Chapter on Contemporary LES Texts, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Xeroxed Materials and Drafts for Chapter 1, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Housing, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Additions for Chap. Hist. Text, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - History Chapter 2 (1 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - History Chapter 2 (2 of 2), undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Permission for MCNY Photos, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Contact Information, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Big Onion Information, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Tenement Museum, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Eldridge Street Project, undates (Box 39, Folder 8)